SO THIS IS
DAY 1
OF TRAINING IN
AI TO BE
MY VIDEO
EDITOR
MY VIDEO ON
X GOT NEARLY
A
MILLION
VIEWS
SOMEONE REPOSTED IT
TO INSTAGRAM
GAVE AWAY MY
DEMO LINK
AND GOT NEARLY
2 ,000
COMMENTS
I GOT
OUTPLAYED
ON MY OWN
WORK
BUT IT GOT
ME TO THINK
I CAN DO
THAT
I MEAN
I'M NOT GOING
TO BECOME AN
EDITOR
BUT I CAN
TEACH AN AI
MAYBE
TO BE AN
EDITOR
FOR ME
SO HERE'S THE
CHALLENGE
30 DAYS
EVERY
EDIT
IS GOING TO
BE MADE BY
AN
AI AGENT
EVERY POST IS
GOING TO BE
MADE BY AN
AI AGENT
AND THE ONLY
RECORDING TOOLS I
CAN USE ARE
MY PHONE AND
MY LAPTOP
STEP ONE WASN'T
EVEN RECORDING
IT WAS OPENING
CLAUDE
I ASKED IT
TO PLAN THE
WHOLE
30 DAYS
FOR ME BEGINNING
TO END THAT'S
WRITE
EDIT
PUBLISH
EVERY DAY
I'M PACKAGING EVERYTHING
INTO A
FREE GUIDE
AND A
CLAUDE PLUGIN
FOLLOW AND COMMENT
DAY 1
AND
I'LL DM YOU
THE LINK